<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paula Branco, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://paobranco.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://paobranco.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Paula Branco, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Paula Branco 2020.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://paobranco.github.io/images/icon_hu37c490c4007590337d0f2ab55cec93b1_41382_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Paula Branco, Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>LIDTA&#39;20 - Tutorial accepted @ ECML/PKDD 2020</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/lidta20tutorialecml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/lidta20tutorialecml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~ltorgo/LIDTA/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LIDTA 2020&lt;/a&gt; is a half day tutorial to be held at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ecmlpkdd2020.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ECML/PKDD’2020&lt;/a&gt;. This tutorial is about Learning with Imbalanced Domains and Rare Event Detection. It targets both newcomers on the subject but also researchers/professionals with previous experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many real-world data-mining applications involve obtaining and evaluating predictive models using data sets with strongly imbalanced distributions of the target variable. Frequently, the least-common values of this target variable are associated with rare events that are highly relevant for end-users. Examples include many diverse domains, such as diagnosis of rare diseases, intrusion detection or popularity prediction in social media. Tackling the issues raised by imbalanced domains is crucial to both academia and industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial clearly describes the full pipeline for rare event detection. This includes i) the fundamentals and principles, ii) methods and evaluation, iii) rare events detection in classified data, iv) explanation, v) a case study on fraud detection in data streams and vi) open challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the tutorial schedule 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~ltorgo/LIDTA/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare Events Detection: Methods and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/talk/lidta20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/talk/lidta20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Rare events detection: Methods and Evaluation&amp;rdquo; September 2020
LIDTA&amp;rsquo;2020: Tutorial on Learning with Imbalanced Domains and Rare Event Detection at ECML/PKDD 2020 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~ltorgo/LIDTA/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tutorial page: 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~ltorgo/LIDTA/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LIDTA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBL R Package - Utility-Based Learning in R</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/ubl/ubl-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/ubl/ubl-description/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UBL&lt;/strong&gt; is an R package developed for &lt;strong&gt;Utility-based Learning&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Utility-based learning problems are framed within predictive analytics tasks. In utility-based learning problems the end-user provides has non uniform preferences regarding the predictive performance of the models. This means that some errors may represent severe consequences while other errors may not be that important. Also the accurate predictions may have different benefits for the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Utility-based learning problems are very frequent in real-world applications. We can find them in medical applications, ecological/meteorological forecasting or in a financial. More information regarding utility-based learning problems can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~branco/PDFfiles/PhDPaulaBranco.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Some solutions for this problem can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~branco/PDFfiles/c6.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~branco/PDFfiles/c7.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~branco/PDFfiles/j14.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The UBL package includes several approaches for dealing with problems with different costs/benefits across the target variable domain. This is a frequent issue in imbalanced domains, so in particular, the implemented approaches are also able to deal with this problem. A detailed explanation of the methods implemented in UBL package can be found 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1604.08079.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cs.dal.ca/~branco/PDFfiles/UBL_R_package_presentation_2018.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to see a presentation of UBL package!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The package is available on 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/paobranco/UBL&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and on 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://CRAN.R-project.org/package=UBL&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CRAN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first R package that integrates methods for dealing with both imbalanced classification and imbalanced regression problems. We also implemented more general methods for dealing with utility-based and cost-sensitive problems. These methods are also implemented for classification and regression tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, and taking into acount only the downloads made through CRAN, the UBL package has a total of 17164 downloads! The last month daily average of UBL downloads is of 36!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below you can observe the daily number of downloads of UBL since its initial release in April 26, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://paobranco.github.io/img/plot1.png&#34; alt=&#34;PLot1&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following figure shows the cummulative number of downloads of UBL from CRAN since its initial release in April 26, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://paobranco.github.io/img/plot2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The package has been improving, and a new release of UBL is being prepared!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download UBL and have fun&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Assistant Professor Position</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/assistant-prof-uottawa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/assistant-prof-uottawa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New tenure track Assistant Professor Position at School of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science at University of Ottawa.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Paper on Discovery Science Conference</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-cure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New paper published on Discovery Science 2019: “The CURE for Class Imbalance&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addressing the class imbalance problem is critical for several real world applications. The application of pre-processing methods is a popular way of dealing with this problem. These solutions increase the rare class examples and/or decrease the normal class cases. However, these procedures typically only take into account the characteristics of each individual class. This segmented view of the data can have a negative impact. We propose a new method that uses an integrated view of the data classes to generate new examples and remove cases. ClUstered REsampling (CURE) is a method based on a holistic view of the data that uses hierarchical clustering and a new distance measure to guide the sampling procedure. Clusters generated in this way take into account the structure of the data. This enables CURE to avoid common mistakes made by other resampling methods. In particular, CURE prevents the generation of synthetic examples in dangerous regions and undersamples safe, non-borderline, regions of the majority class. We show the effectiveness of CURE in an extensive set of experiments with benchmark domains. We also show that CURE is a user-friendly method that does not require extensive fine-tuning of hyper-parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CURE for Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c15/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Study on the Impact of Data Characteristics in Imbalanced Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c14/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Paper on DSAA 2019 Conference</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-dsaa2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-dsaa2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New paper published on DSAA 2019: &amp;ldquo;A Study on the Impact of Data Characteristics in Imbalanced Regression Tasks&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The class imbalance problem has been thoroughly studied over the past two decades. More recently, the research community realized that the problem of imbalanced distributions also occurred in other tasks beyond classification. Regression problems are among these newly studied tasks where the problem of imbalanced domains also poses important challenges. Imbalanced regression problems occur in a diversity of real world domains such as meteorological (predicting weather extreme values), financial (extreme stock returns forecasting) or medical (anticipate rare values). In imbalanced regression the end-user preferences are biased towards values of the target variable that are under-represented on the available data. Several pre-processing methods were proposed to address this problem. These methods change the training set to force the learner to focus on the rare cases. However, as far as we know, the relationship between the data intrinsic characteristics and the performance achieved by these methods has not yet been studied for imbalanced regression tasks. In this paper we describe a study of the impact certain data characteristics may have in the results of applying pre-processing methods to imbalanced regression problems. To achieve this goal, we define potentially interesting data characteristics of regression problems. We then conduct our study using a synthetic data repository build for this purpose. We show that all the different characteristics studied have a different behaviour that is related with the level at which the data characteristic is present and the learning algorithm used. The main contributions of our work are: i) to define interesting data characteristics for regression tasks; ii) to create the first repository of imbalanced regression tasks containing 6000 data sets with controlled data characteristics; and iii) to provide insights on the impact of intrinsic data characteristics in the results of pre-processing methods for handling imbalanced regression tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-processing approaches for imbalanced distributions in regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Paper in Neurocomputing Journal</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-neurocomputing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/new-paper-neurocomputing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New paper published on Neurocomputing Journal: “Pre-processing Approaches for Imbalanced Distributions” DOI:10.1016/j.neucom.2018.11.100.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imbalanced domains are an important problem frequently arising in real world predictive analytics. A significant body of research has addressed imbalanced distributions in classification tasks, where the target variable is nominal. In the context of regression tasks, where the target variable is continuous, imbalanced distributions of the target variable also raise several challenges to learning algorithms. Imbalanced domains are characterized by: (1) a higher relevance being assigned to the performance on a subset of the target variable values; and (2) these most relevant values being underrepresented on the available data set. Recently, some proposals were made to address the problem of imbalanced distributions in regression. Still, this remains a scarcely explored issue with few existing solutions. This paper describes three new approaches for tackling the problem of imbalanced distributions in regression tasks. We propose the adaptation to regression tasks of random over-sampling and introduction of Gaussian Noise, and we present a new method called WEighted Relevance-based Combination Strategy (WERCS). An extensive set of experiments provides empirical evidence of the advantage of using the proposed strategies and, in particular, the WERCS  method. We analyze the impact of different data characteristics in the performance of the methods. A data repository with 15 imbalanced regression data sets is also provided to the research community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New PostDoctoral Fellowship</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/postdoc-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/postdoc-start/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PostDoc at Dalhousie University under the supervision of Professor Luis Torgo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PostDoc theme is &amp;ldquo;Methods for Handling Problems with Domain-specific Utility Preference Biases&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebagg: Resampled bagging for imbalanced regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c12/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetaUtil: Meta learning for utility maximization in regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c11/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Defense - Utility-based Predictive Analytics</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/news/defense-phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/news/defense-phd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In several predictive tasks the end-user attention is focused in certain regions of the domain of the target variable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As opposed to standard predictive tasks where all target variable values are equally important, in these particular tasks the domain has a non-uniform importance for the end-user.
In many real world domains, such as financial, meteorological or medical, we can find tasks that fit into this non-standard setting.
In effect, for most practical applications we  observe  that  there  is  important  domain  knowledge  that  must  be  accounted  for  when solving the corresponding predictive task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these tasks, the relevance of certain regions of the domain is associated to either high costs and/or severe consequences, or to important profits and/or benefits.
Initially, the research community  addressed  these  tasks  through  the  development  of  the  cost-sensitive  learning theory which considers only the costs component.  More recently, this theory evolved to the broader  framework  of  utility-based  mining.   The  utility-based  learning  setting  allows  the consideration of both costs and benefits that may derive from different domain information. Although more complex, the utility-based learning framework is also more intuitive from an end-user perspective and more thorough regarding the domain information representation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first efforts for including costs and benefits into the learning procedure were concentrated in tasks with a nominal target variable (classification tasks).  Still, with time, it became clear that this learning paradigm was also applicable to regression tasks, where the target variable is continuous.  In this thesis we focus on the utility-based learning problem.  The youth of this broader approach, specially regarding regression tasks, results in the existence of several open issues that we tackled.  In particular, we identified and addressed the following main challenges: i) development of a unifying framework for utility-based learning; ii) developmentof learning methods for optimising utility in regression tasks; and iii) proposal of new pre-processing methods for addressing the problem of learning from imbalanced domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proposal of a unifying utility-based framework allows to better understand the characteristics of these tasks, while integrating both classification and regression problems.  Moreover, using this framework we are also able to establish important connections between different predictive problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second challenge is related with the lack of methods to address utility-based regression problems. When dealing with utility-based learning if the utility information is not incorporated into the learning procedure we are only able to obtain sub-optimal models.  To solve this problem we propose and evaluate new methods that allow to maximise the utility in regression.  We show that these methods are effective for different utility settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third and final challenge is related with the particular sub-class of utility-based problems known as imbalanced domains.  This is also a problem insufficiently studied in the context of regression tasks.  We propose and evaluate several approaches to address this problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a practical outcome of this work, we provide UBL, an R package for utility-based learning that integrates approaches for classification and regression tasks.  The UBL package includes the proposals presented in this thesis, as well as many other approaches developed for utility-based classification, providing to the research community a tool for testing and comparing different alternative methods of addressing utility-based predictive tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resampling with neighbourhood bias on imbalanced domains</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Workshop on Learning with Imbalanced Domains: Preface</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Sensitive Learning: Preface</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c13/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ensemble methods in imbalanced regression tasks</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring resampling with neighborhood bias on imbalanced regression problems</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c8/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning through utility optimization in regression tasks</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Imbalanced Domains: Preface</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relevance-based evaluation metrics for multi-class imbalanced domains</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c9/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMOGN: a pre-processing approach for imbalanced regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resampling strategies for imbalanced time series forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A framework for recommendation of highly popular news lacking social feedback</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A survey of predictive modeling on imbalanced domains</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resampling strategies for imbalanced time series</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime prediction using regression and resources optimization</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resampling strategies for regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/j1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMOTE for Regression</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/publication/c1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
