<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Projects | Paula Branco, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Open Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Paula Branco 2021.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://paobranco.github.io/images/icon_hu37c490c4007590337d0f2ab55cec93b1_41382_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Open Projects</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduate Projects</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/gradprojects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/gradprojects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New paper published on Neurocomputing Journal: “Pre-processing Approaches for Imbalanced Distributions” DOI:10.1016/j.neucom.2018.11.100.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imbalanced domains are an important problem frequently arising in real world predictive analytics. A significant body of research has addressed imbalanced distributions in classification tasks, where the target variable is nominal. In the context of regression tasks, where the target variable is continuous, imbalanced distributions of the target variable also raise several challenges to learning algorithms. Imbalanced domains are characterized by: (1) a higher relevance being assigned to the performance on a subset of the target variable values; and (2) these most relevant values being underrepresented on the available data set. Recently, some proposals were made to address the problem of imbalanced distributions in regression. Still, this remains a scarcely explored issue with few existing solutions. This paper describes three new approaches for tackling the problem of imbalanced distributions in regression tasks. We propose the adaptation to regression tasks of random over-sampling and introduction of Gaussian Noise, and we present a new method called WEighted Relevance-based Combination Strategy (WERCS). An extensive set of experiments provides empirical evidence of the advantage of using the proposed strategies and, in particular, the WERCS  method. We analyze the impact of different data characteristics in the performance of the methods. A data repository with 15 imbalanced regression data sets is also provided to the research community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Projects</title>
      <link>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/undergradprojects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paobranco.github.io/openprojects/undergradprojects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;--using-machine-learning-for-rare-disease-detection&#34;&gt;- Using Machine Learning for Rare Disease Detection.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-project-will-be-co-supervised-by-dr-matthew-henderson-laboratory-head-of-biochemistry-and-point-of-care-screening-from-newborn-screening-ontario-nso&#34;&gt;This project will be co-supervised by Dr. Matthew Henderson (Laboratory Head of Biochemistry and Point of Care Screening) from Newborn Screening Ontario (NSO).&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;--building-and-improving-a-webapp-for-an-health-application-adding-new-and-improving-existing-features-adding-new-security-measures&#34;&gt;- Building and improving a webapp for an health application (adding new and improving existing features, adding new security measures).&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-project-will-be-co-supervised-by-prof-karine-toupin-april-adjunct-professor-with-the-school-of-rehabilitation-sciences-in-the-university-of-ottawas-faculty-of-health-sciences&#34;&gt;This project will be co-supervised by Prof. Karine Toupin-April (Adjunct Professor with the School of Rehabilitation Sciences in the University of Ottawa’s Faculty of Health Sciences).&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;heading-1&#34;&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create this and that&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
